分隔的世界
Worlds so far apart
被遺忘的心
hearts hung out to dry
我仍想問好
They'll have my regards
只望有時間
just wish we had time
已經過太久
It's been much too long
自從上次見
since I've their eyes
放手的念頭
Trying to let go
我從未想過
was never on my mind
但誰能從，謊言中分出現實
But who can tell lies from reality
當每個人看法一致？
when everyone sees the same?
誰又能夠，寫下銀河的每一哩
And who can spell out
the miles of the galaxies
當它就是太多空間？
when there's just too much space?
而它就是太多空間
And there's just too much space
聽好你字句
Listen to your words
否則就成玩物
or they will pass you by
每個人聽見
Everyone who heard
都會看穿謊言
will see right through your lies
想像自己與星群，飄在太空中
It's not hard to imagine
yourself out in space
的確很簡單
floating with the stars
但當真的發生時，
But with everything that happens,
在那處境下
happening all around you
你也不再是你
It's just not who you are
但誰能從，謊言中分出現實
But who can tell lies from reality
當每個人看法一致？
when everyone sees the same?
誰又能夠，寫下銀河的每一哩
And who can spell out
the miles of the galaxies
當它就是太多空間？
when there's just too much space?
而它就是太多空間
And there's just too much space
你是否會屏棄你所知一切？
Would you turn your back
on everything you know?
並且不往回看，並且不知道去向？
and not look back,
and not know where to go?
分隔的世界
Worlds so far apart
被遺忘的心
hearts hung out to dry
我仍想問好
They'll have my regards
他們一直在心上
they're always on my mind
但誰能從，謊言中分出現實
But who can tell lies from reality
當每個人看法一致？
when everyone sees the same?
誰又能夠，寫下銀河的每一哩
And who can spell out
the miles of the galaxies
當它就是太多空間？
when there's just too much space?
而它就是太多空間
And there's just too much space